<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<news-item-result><news-item news-item-id="1"><news-item-title><![CDATA[Real Weddings website launches in style]]></news-item-title><news-item-publish-date><![CDATA[2010-03-09]]></news-item-publish-date><news-item-body><![CDATA[<p>The Real Weddings team hosted a stylish soire in St Kilda to celebrate the launch of their new website. Flint loves a party so we attended in force enjoying champagne and the delicious miniature morsels from catering company &quot;food&amp;desire&quot;. Yum!</p><p>Check out the gorgeous <a href="http://www.realweddings.com.au" target="_blank">Real Weddings website.</a> </p><p>Image credit: <a href="http://foodanddesire.com/" target="_blank">food&amp;desire</a> and <a href="http://www.blumenthalphotography.com.au/" target="_blank" title="Blumenthal Photography">Blumenthal Photography<br /><br /></a> </p>]]></news-item-body><news-item-hero-image><![CDATA[<photos><photo><file><![CDATA[/news/realweddingslaunch/realweddings_launch.png]]]]><![CDATA[></file><source-width>730</source-width><source-height>300</source-height><source-size bytes="131229">128.15 kB</source-size><title><![CDATA[corby 1]]]]><![CDATA[></title></photo></photos>]]></news-item-hero-image><news-item-photos><![CDATA[<photos></photos>]]></news-item-photos></news-item><news-item news-item-id="2"><news-item-title><![CDATA[Flint attends L'Oréal Melbourne Fashion Festival partners night]]></news-item-title><news-item-publish-date><![CDATA[2010-02-10]]></news-item-publish-date><news-item-body><![CDATA[<p>The LMFF team hosted a generous partners celebration at the State Library. The event was hosted by Lauren Brain, presenter on NOVA 100, who led expert panel to talk about the their successful partnerships with LMFF. </p><p>Flint Interactive is working with LMFF as their web development partner on the 2010 L&#39;Or&eacute;al Melbourne Fashion Festival. View information about the <a href="/work/project-information/loreal-melbourne-fashion-festival">L&#39;Or&eacute;al Melbourne Fashion Festival website development</a>. </p>]]></news-item-body><news-item-hero-image><![CDATA[<photos><photo><file><![CDATA[/news/partnerscelebration/partners_celebration.png]]]]><![CDATA[></file><source-width>730</source-width><source-height>300</source-height><source-size bytes="128353">125.34 kB</source-size><title><![CDATA[news]]]]><![CDATA[></title></photo></photos>]]></news-item-hero-image><news-item-photos><![CDATA[<photos></photos>]]></news-item-photos></news-item><news-item news-item-id="3"><news-item-title><![CDATA[Flint attends L'Oréal Melbourne Fashion Festival program launch]]></news-item-title><news-item-publish-date><![CDATA[2010-02-16]]></news-item-publish-date><news-item-body><![CDATA[<p>Flint attended the glam and gorgeous 2010 L&#39;Or&eacute;al Melbourne Fashion Festival at Federation Square. Get ready to get happy at this year&#39;s Festival - which promises to be bigger and better than ever.</p><p>Checkout the <a href="http://www.lmff.com.au" target="_blank">LMFF website.</a> &nbsp; <br /><br />Image credit: <a href="http://www.lucasdawson.com.au/main.php" target="_blank">Lucas Dawson</a></p>]]></news-item-body><news-item-hero-image><![CDATA[<photos><photo><file><![CDATA[/news/programlaunch/LMFF_ProgramLaunch.png]]]]><![CDATA[></file><source-width>730</source-width><source-height>300</source-height><source-size bytes="142803">139.46 kB</source-size><title><![CDATA[program launch 33 ]]]]><![CDATA[></title></photo></photos>]]></news-item-hero-image><news-item-photos><![CDATA[<photos></photos>]]></news-item-photos></news-item><news-item news-item-id="4"><news-item-title><![CDATA[Flint prepares for the Melbourne Food & Wine Festival]]></news-item-title><news-item-publish-date><![CDATA[2010-03-02]]></news-item-publish-date><news-item-body><![CDATA[With a gorgeous new website in place we are poised and ready for the Melbourne Food &amp; Wine Festival to hit! Flint started celebrating early at the MFW hosted Crawl and Bite partner celebration on March 2nd. The Festival team showed they can really host a party taking us on a gourmet tour of Melbourne&#39;s back streets - with an Asian feast from Longrain, Seamstress and Mask of China. Delicious!!<br /><br />Visit the <a href="http://www.melbournefoodandwine.com.au" target="_blank">Melbourne Food &amp; Wine Festival website</a> and join in the foodie fun!]]></news-item-body><news-item-hero-image><![CDATA[<photos><photo><file><![CDATA[/news/crawlbite/crawlandbite.png]]]]><![CDATA[></file><source-width>730</source-width><source-height>300</source-height><source-size bytes="129752">126.71 kB</source-size><title><![CDATA[crawlandbite]]]]><![CDATA[></title></photo></photos>]]></news-item-hero-image><news-item-photos><![CDATA[<photos></photos>]]></news-item-photos></news-item><news-item news-item-id="6"><news-item-title><![CDATA[Stephanie Alexander Kitchen Garden Foundation chooses Flint!]]></news-item-title><news-item-publish-date><![CDATA[2010-03-11]]></news-item-publish-date><news-item-body><![CDATA[<p>We are so thrilled to be working with this incredible and dynamic organisation as their new website partner. Looking forward to diving into the first planning workshop this week!</p><p>Learn more about <a href="http://www.kitchengardenfoundation.org.au" target="_blank">the Stephanie Alexander Kitchen Garden Foundation here. </a><br />And watch this URL for an amazing new website soon! </p>]]></news-item-body><news-item-hero-image><![CDATA[<photos><photo><file><![CDATA[/news/stephanie/stephanie2.png]]]]><![CDATA[></file><source-width>730</source-width><source-height>300</source-height><source-size bytes="124128">121.22 kB</source-size><title><![CDATA[stephanie]]]]><![CDATA[></title></photo></photos>]]></news-item-hero-image><news-item-photos><![CDATA[<photos></photos>]]></news-item-photos></news-item><news-item news-item-id="7"><news-item-title><![CDATA[A Fashion Packed Week for Flint]]></news-item-title><news-item-publish-date><![CDATA[2010-03-23]]></news-item-publish-date><news-item-introduction><![CDATA[<p>Flint enjoyed a massive week of champagne and fashion at LMFF! The Festival launched last Sunday with a delightful garden party at Government House and kicked on through the week with the L&#39;Or&eacute;al Paris Runways shows and business seminars. </p>]]></news-item-introduction><news-item-body><![CDATA[The LMFF website reflected  all Festival events as they happened with a jam packed image gallery and  LMFF TV section.<a href="http://www.lmff.com.au" target="_blank"> Check it  out here. </a><br /><br />Image credit: <a href="http://www.backstagefix.com" target="_blank">Backstage Fix</a><br /> ]]></news-item-body><news-item-hero-image><![CDATA[<photos><photo><file><![CDATA[/news/fashionweek/fashion-packed-week.jpg]]]]><![CDATA[></file><source-width>730</source-width><source-height>300</source-height><source-size bytes="66222">64.67 kB</source-size><title><![CDATA[fashion packed week]]]]><![CDATA[></title></photo></photos>]]></news-item-hero-image><news-item-photos><![CDATA[<photos></photos>]]></news-item-photos></news-item><news-item news-item-id="8"><news-item-title><![CDATA[Dumplings, French Delights and Cellar Door at MFW]]></news-item-title><news-item-publish-date><![CDATA[2010-03-23]]></news-item-publish-date><news-item-introduction><![CDATA[<p>Flint ate, drank and was very, very merry at the Melbourne Food &amp; Wine Festival this week. <br /></p>]]></news-item-introduction><news-item-body><![CDATA[We put in an excellent foodie effort this week - from the bustling Hawkers Market (mmm  dumplings) to champagne and French pastries at the Langham afternoon tea  through to yesterday&#39;s glorious Cellar Door at Southbank. <br /><br />Check out more on the <a href="http://www.melbournefoodandwine.com.au" target="_blank">Melbourne Food &amp; Wine website.</a>]]></news-item-body><news-item-hero-image><![CDATA[<photos><photo><file><![CDATA[/news/mfwweek/dumplings-fresh-delights.jpg]]]]><![CDATA[></file><source-width>730</source-width><source-height>300</source-height><source-size bytes="66312">64.76 kB</source-size><title><![CDATA[dumplings fresh delights]]]]><![CDATA[></title></photo></photos>]]></news-item-hero-image><news-item-photos><![CDATA[<photos></photos>]]></news-item-photos></news-item><news-item news-item-id="9"><news-item-title><![CDATA[New Flint HQ!]]></news-item-title><news-item-publish-date><![CDATA[2010-04-01]]></news-item-publish-date><news-item-introduction><![CDATA[Flint has packed up shop and moved to Easey Street!]]></news-item-introduction><news-item-body><![CDATA[<p>&nbsp;</p><p>Literally just around the corner, we moved into our brand new home on Friday after a massive day of packing, shuffling, cleaning and heavy lifting. Visit us at:</p><p>20 Easey Street, Collingwood </p>]]></news-item-body><news-item-hero-image><![CDATA[<photos><photo><file><![CDATA[/news/flinthq/flint-moves-office.jpg]]]]><![CDATA[></file><source-width>730</source-width><source-height>300</source-height><source-size bytes="71397">69.72 kB</source-size><title><![CDATA[flint moves office]]]]><![CDATA[></title></photo></photos>]]></news-item-hero-image><news-item-photos><![CDATA[<photos></photos>]]></news-item-photos></news-item><news-item news-item-id="10"><news-item-title><![CDATA[Flint opens studio to Design Students]]></news-item-title><news-item-publish-date><![CDATA[2010-04-28]]></news-item-publish-date><news-item-body><![CDATA[<h3>Flint Interactive was chosen to be the Web Partner for the 2010 AGIdeas event held in April. AGIdeas presents a series of events for designers who are seeking inspiration, for designers emerging in the industry to explore the possibilities of careers in design and for companies looking to embrace design as an economic driver. </h3> As a passionate web design agency we got involve by opening our studio up to 10 design students as part of the AGIdeas Studio Access program. This event is to gain insights into different methods and practices in different design studios. <br /> <br /> Flint introduced students to the world of web design and development and gave the opportunity to learn about the way we approach design projects online. Students were taken through some of our work, given tips about designing for the web, and taken through a project approach where students developed wireframes for a project. After, QA time was given, with many chocolates and gifts given out to people with good questions.<br /> <br /> The event we feel was a great success being our first involvement with AGIdeas and opening our studio to students. We loved the opportunity to speak to these design students and hope that they feel inspired to explore more of what the digital medium has to offer. <br /> <br /> We intend on running other sessions for design students through-out the year and possibly exploring opening up a night for aspiring web developers. If anyone is interested in attending these events or would like to be kept informed of when these events will be occurring, follow us on twitter: @<a href="http://twitter.com/Flint_Tweets">Flint_Tweets</a>.<br /> ]]></news-item-body><news-item-hero-image><![CDATA[<photos><photo><file><![CDATA[/news/agideas-news.jpg]]]]><![CDATA[></file><source-width>730</source-width><source-height>300</source-height><source-size bytes="79646">77.78 kB</source-size><title><![CDATA[agideas news]]]]><![CDATA[></title></photo></photos>]]></news-item-hero-image><news-item-photos><![CDATA[<photos></photos>]]></news-item-photos></news-item><news-item news-item-id="11"><news-item-title><![CDATA[Flint helps mag nation double online conversion]]></news-item-title><news-item-publish-date><![CDATA[2010-06-25]]></news-item-publish-date><news-item-introduction><![CDATA[<p>Flint was involved in the redevelopment of the e-commerce subscription process for mag nation, providing a new approach to their checkout process and introducing a PayPal express checkout for customers which has lead to a double in their conversion rate.</p>]]></news-item-introduction><news-item-body><![CDATA[<div>Flint has had a long standing relationship with mag nation, building their website and helping establish some very cool functionality for consumers (genius Sahil Merchant and his team have fantastic ideas), and develop backend systems for assisting with the operational management of online subscriptions.</div><div>&nbsp;</div><div>View the <a href="http://www.flintinteractive.com.au/work/project-information/mag-nation">mag nation project info</a> in our folio.&nbsp;</div><div><br /></div><div>Recently mag nation has been focusing on improving conversion of online magazine subscriptions as the website traffic has been increasing. Many companies after launching websites learn a lot from their customers and identify opportunities to improve based on what their customers want, and is incredibly important in online space to test, monitor and improve. Through directly engaging their customers through croud-sourcing and using analytics to help analyse the checkout process, it was identified that an improvement to checkout would provide a big improvement.</div><div><br /></div><div>Initially stipulated as a design challenge and slight change of process, Flint suggested a full implementation of a checkout process that we had recently carefully designed and developed and had put to the test.</div><div><br /></div><div>Flint solution involved introducing a 3 step checkout to simplify the process for the end customer, a new simplified layout with the introduction of Guest checkout and PayPal express checkout (allowing customers to use their payment and address details stored in their PayPal account). The process makes it much easier for the customer to make a purchase and provides them more flexibility about managing their personal details.</div><div><br /></div><div>In the last week since the website has been launched the website has been reported to have doubled online subscriptions.</div><div><br /></div><div>Both Flint and the client are ecstatic.&nbsp;</div><div><br /></div><div>In the next couple of weeks a series of additional front-end enhancements will be developed and put live, as well as some great creative thinking by mag nation into some additional kickers for subscriptions. We look forward to the next phase of updates going live and are eager to see the improvements put into action.</div><div><br /></div><div>Flint has had a long relationship with mag nation and are passionate behind the mag nation brand. Flint has developed mag nation full website backend management infrastructure both for site content management as well as for member and magazine fulfilment. The system manages the internal workflow of a users subscription, generating reports, product pricing data and managing publishers for direct and local subscriptions.</div><div><br /></div><div>Developing a custom e-commerce system has provided great flexibility for the creative brand genius of mag nation. Mag nation&#39;s challenge is both a brand challenge as much as an operational challenge. Much complexity exists in their subscription offers, such as supporting; buy this issue, buy next issue, buy 6 months, 1 year, 2 years, new zealand sales, australia sales and international sales, direct sales and local publishers, bi-annual magazines, 52 issue magazines etc etc. This has lead to some big development and operational considerations in which Flint has helped develop a solution to the challenge. &nbsp;</div><div>&nbsp;</div><div>Learn more about <a href="http://www.flintinteractive.com.au/services/ecommerce">ecommerce systems</a> design and development services from Flint&nbsp;</div>]]></news-item-body><news-item-hero-image><![CDATA[<photos></photos>]]></news-item-hero-image><news-item-photos><![CDATA[<photos></photos>]]></news-item-photos></news-item><news-item news-item-id="12"><news-item-title><![CDATA[Real Weddings Official Honouree 2010 Webby Awards]]></news-item-title><news-item-publish-date><![CDATA[2010-05-12]]></news-item-publish-date><news-item-introduction><![CDATA[<p><strong>Flint has assisted Real Weddings designing and developing a new website which has earned a Official Honoree in the 2010 Webby Awards in two categories, lifestyle and magazine, along side great sites such as Nike+, Martha Stewart, GQ and InStyle.</strong></p><p>&nbsp;</p>]]></news-item-introduction><news-item-body><![CDATA[<blockquote style="margin-top: 0px; margin-right: 0px; margin-bottom: 0px; margin-left: 40px; border-width: initial; border-color: initial; border-style: none; padding: 0px"><p>&nbsp;</p><p><em>The Webby Awards is the leading international award honoring excellence on the Internet. Established in 1996 during the Web&#39;s infancy, the Webbys are presented by The International Academy of Digital Arts and Sciences, which includes an Executive 750-member body of leading Web experts, business figures, luminaries, visionaries and creative celebrities, and Associate Members who are former Webby Award Winners and Nominees and other Internet professionals.</em></p></blockquote><p>&nbsp;</p><p>Flint Interactive designed and developed a website for Real Weddings that was launched in January 2010. The website provides a unique offering for brides mixing a paid content subscription model for premium content. It&#39;s the kind of content that lets brides be unique and execute an amazing wedding. </p><p>Working with the look and feel of Real Weddings, Flint successfully brought their brand essence to life online and implemented an online website containing an enormous repository of inspirational wedding stories and photos, full-screen video content and really useful resources such as a directory of premium providers, honeymoon destinations and postcards, as well as a forum.</p><p>As a content producer and publisher, Real Weddings had many opportunities to provide advertising on their website. Flint created unique video players to allow opportunities to sell advertising space, as well as implementing an extremely advanced banner/ad server management solution to support additional revenue through advertising.</p><p>The challenge was both one of getting the branding perfect, and solving a challenge to the traditional pricing model of online content - introducing paid content. Flint developed a system to allow users to &#39;peak&#39; at areas of content, but required a year subscription for full access.&nbsp;</p><p>The challenge was unique and required an enourmous effort, and a great investment by everyone in the team. The process was rewarding, and the end result was beautiful. What an outstanding reward having the website be recognised by the Webby Awards, along side great sites such as Nike+ and Martha Stewart.</p><p>Congratulations Real Weddings team, I think we achieved an awesome result.&nbsp;</p><p><a href="http://www.flintinteractive.com.au/work/project-information/real-weddings">Have a look at the project</a>.&nbsp;</p>]]></news-item-body><news-item-hero-image><![CDATA[<photos></photos>]]></news-item-hero-image><news-item-photos><![CDATA[<photos></photos>]]></news-item-photos></news-item><news-item news-item-id="13"><news-item-title><![CDATA[Flint reappointed as the official Web Partner for AgIdeas in 2011]]></news-item-title><news-item-publish-date><![CDATA[2010-07-15]]></news-item-publish-date><news-item-body><![CDATA[<p>&nbsp;</p><p>This will be our second year of involvement with AgIdeas, having taken part in a successful 2010 event where we opened our studio doors to 10 aspiring design students. To read more about what happened, <a href="/news/46/10/flint-opens-studio-to-design-students/">click here</a>.&nbsp;</p><p>The next AgIdeas will take place in May 2011 and includes an international design forum, studio visits, workshops, secondary school evenings, a gala dinner and a huge after party. Since its inception in 1991, 390 of the world&rsquo;s leading designers have inspired over 37,500 designers.&nbsp;</p><p>Flint is proud to be part of such a prestigious event and we look forward to working with AgIdeas in the coming months. We will keep you posted on further developments.&nbsp;</p><div><br /></div><p>&nbsp;</p>]]></news-item-body><news-item-hero-image><![CDATA[<photos></photos>]]></news-item-hero-image><news-item-photos><![CDATA[<photos></photos>]]></news-item-photos></news-item><news-item news-item-id="14"><news-item-title><![CDATA[GAP says Hello Australia...and Busbrands chose Flint to be their digital agency!]]></news-item-title><news-item-publish-date><![CDATA[2010-07-19]]></news-item-publish-date><news-item-body><![CDATA[<div>To coincide with its highly anticipated Australian launch, iconic international brand Gap has appointed Flint Interactive as its digital agency. &nbsp;</div><div><br /></div><div>Since 1969, customers have looked to Gap for updated, casual clothing and accessories that help them express their own personal sense of style. Today, Gap continues to be the best destination for wardrobe essentials such as T-shirts, hoodies, great-fitting pants and denim.&nbsp;</div><div><br /></div><div>The result of our collaboration with Gap can already be seen at <a href="http://www.gapaustralia.com/">www.gapaustralia.com</a>, which launched recently to offer consumers a sneak peak at the brand while allowing them to sign up for exclusive updates about Gap&rsquo;s impending store openings.&nbsp;</div><div><br /></div><div>&ldquo;We are excited to have partnered with Flint Interactive and we are thrilled with the Gap site. &nbsp;We feel the site effectively showcases the essence of the Gap brand while allowing us to capture consumer data and capitalise on early interest surrounding the brand&rsquo;s launch,&rdquo; says YC Eu, Group Marketing Manager of Busby Holdings.</div><div><br /></div><div>Gap&rsquo;s first flagship store will open at Chadstone Shopping Centre in mid August to coincide with the brand&rsquo;s much anticipated Australian launch. &nbsp;The second Gap store will open in Westfield Sydney at the end of October 2010.</div>]]></news-item-body><news-item-hero-image><![CDATA[<photos></photos>]]></news-item-hero-image><news-item-photos><![CDATA[<photos></photos>]]></news-item-photos></news-item><news-item news-item-id="16"><news-item-title><![CDATA[Welcome to the world of MOR: MOR Cosmetics launches its new online store]]></news-item-title><news-item-publish-date><![CDATA[2010-07-20]]></news-item-publish-date><news-item-body><![CDATA[MOR Cosmetics is an Australian brand that is recognised globally for its range of innovative and luxurious body care and lifestyle products.&nbsp;Having cultivated an international following, MOR Cosmetics needed a website that would allow their products to be purchased from Australia and overseas. <br /><br />The philosophy behind MOR is to provide a personalised sensory journey and a&nbsp;memorable pampering experience.&nbsp;In partnership with MOR, who designed the site interface, Flint worked to&nbsp;create an e-boutique store that showcased MOR&#39;s products in all its decadent glory. <a href="/work/project-information/mor-cosmetics">Check it out here</a>. ]]></news-item-body><news-item-hero-image><![CDATA[<photos></photos>]]></news-item-hero-image><news-item-photos><![CDATA[<photos></photos>]]></news-item-photos></news-item><news-item news-item-id="17"><news-item-title><![CDATA[Get ready for the upcoming Young Guns of Wine Festival]]></news-item-title><news-item-publish-date><![CDATA[2010-07-23]]></news-item-publish-date><news-item-body><![CDATA[<p>Taking place between August 8 to 16, the Young Guns of Wine Festival is a celebration of Australia&#39;s finest young winemakers. </p><p>With the event being held at a number of Melbourne&#39;s best restaurants, this burgeoning festival, now in its third year, wanted to stand out from other food and wine events in Australia. </p><p>Working with 3 deep design, who art directed the visual identity of the festival, Flint created a website that reflects the youth and vitality of our next generation of winemakers.&nbsp; </p><p>Be sure to go to the <a href="/work/project-information/young-guns-of-wine">website</a> and start planning your event. You&#39;ll enjoy a memorable night out with outstanding food matched with great wine. </p>]]></news-item-body><news-item-hero-image><![CDATA[<photos></photos>]]></news-item-hero-image><news-item-photos><![CDATA[<photos></photos>]]></news-item-photos></news-item><news-item news-item-id="18"><news-item-title><![CDATA[Flint attends the High Calibre Marketing conference at the Young Guns of Wine Festival]]></news-item-title><news-item-publish-date><![CDATA[2010-08-17]]></news-item-publish-date><news-item-introduction><![CDATA[Flint Interactive was invited to the &quot;High Calibre Marketing&quot; conference at the Young Guns of Wine Festival, which was held at the chic surrounds of Comme. As a festival that celebrates new and innovative wine makers, it was fitting that YGOW offered professionals in the wine industry the chance to hear from people who shared their insights on marketing and communications from the perspective of their own industries. Why was Flint there? Because many of these innovations have come from online media - and that is what Flint is about. <br /><br />Speakers included Barrie Barton from Right Angle Publishing, Brett Philips - Principal of 3 deep design and Grant Smillie - Nova FM host and owner of Neon Records. They covered topics that ranged from the effect of lifestyle and population trends, to the power of innovation and the influence of the emergence of social media. <br /><br />We will be taking away some of our observations and reporting them back to the team at Flint. ]]></news-item-introduction><news-item-hero-image><![CDATA[<photos></photos>]]></news-item-hero-image><news-item-photos><![CDATA[<photos></photos>]]></news-item-photos></news-item><news-item news-item-id="19"><news-item-title><![CDATA[Positions available at Flint]]></news-item-title><news-item-publish-date><![CDATA[2010-08-24]]></news-item-publish-date><news-item-body><![CDATA[<p>Calling all brilliant PHP web developers! We currently have vacancies for mid and senior level web developers at Flint.&nbsp; We also seek an ingenious Senior Flash developer. For further information, please take a look at the following job descriptions:</p><h3><span class="feature-text"><a href="/join-us/senior-php-developer">Senior PHP Developer</a><br /><a href="/join-us/midweight-php-developer">Mid-level PHP Developer</a><br /><a href="/join-us/senior-flash-developer">Senior Flash Developer</a></span>  <br /> </h3><h1> </h1><p>Flint will be taking on a number of new and interesting projects over the coming months and we will need talented people to join our team as we grow in size and reputation. These positions include:</p><h4><span class="feature-text">- Designer<br />- Project Manager<br />- Senior Interactive Developer<br />- Contract Designer<br />- Freelance Junior Flash Developer<br />- Freelance Senior Flash Developer<br />- Freelance EDM coder</span><br /></h4><p>If you like what we do and you think you have that something special to offer, please keep an eye out as we advertise for these positions on our website. </p>]]></news-item-body><news-item-hero-image><![CDATA[<photos></photos>]]></news-item-hero-image><news-item-photos><![CDATA[<photos></photos>]]></news-item-photos></news-item><news-item news-item-id="21"><news-item-title><![CDATA[Melbourne Food and Wine Festival Events Launching December 3]]></news-item-title><news-item-publish-date><![CDATA[2010-11-03]]></news-item-publish-date><news-item-body><![CDATA[<p>The Melbourne Food and Wine Festival is a highlight of the Melbourne Food and Wine calendar. This is the second year that Flint has partnered with Melbourne Food and Wine to develop a captivating website for the event. A number of significant new features have been added to the website--these include a new venue pages with profiles on the locations where the events take place, and new regional pages that will focus on different areas of Victoria, showcasing the diversity of food and wine to be found.&nbsp; </p><p> We&#39;ve also made improvements to existing elements on the site. Bringing the event into the social media age, you can now share the events that you&#39;re interested in attending on twitter and facebook.&nbsp;  </p><p>You can already go to the festival website and explore the great masterclass events that are on offer but the final phase will be going live on December 3, coinciding with the official program launch. What you can expect is a new &#39;My Festival Planner&#39; that allows you to plan your own festival diary and you will be able to browse the complete listing of festival events. This event keeps getting bigger and better and we can&#39;t wait for it to all unfold over ten days in March. We even built a countdown clock to keep track of the days until the event and in keeping with the theme, we have integrated it with a clever animation of wine drops falling into a glass from a wine bottle!&nbsp;&nbsp;</p><p>Click <a href="http://www.melbournefoodandwine.com.au/">here</a> to check out the website! </p>]]></news-item-body><news-item-hero-image><![CDATA[<photos></photos>]]></news-item-hero-image><news-item-photos><![CDATA[<photos></photos>]]></news-item-photos></news-item><news-item news-item-id="22"><news-item-title><![CDATA[Two green thumbs up for the Stephanie Alexander Kitchen Garden Foundation website!]]></news-item-title><news-item-publish-date><![CDATA[2010-10-04]]></news-item-publish-date><news-item-body><![CDATA[<p>Flint Interactive has recently completed the mammoth task of creating the Stephanie Alexander Kitchen Garden Foundation Website. This program started in Collingwood, where Flint is also a local, and has grown to include 139 primary schools all around Australia. The aim of the program is to change the way children approach and think about food. It has been a massive undertaking with an online store, resources, news, photo and video content, interactive maps, member&#39;s pages and comprehensive information of the program all neatly packaged onto the site. </p><p>  We&#39;ve been told that Stephanie herself is extremely pleased with the result--here&#39;s what Claire from the foundation had to say: &quot;The new site is a wonderful reflection of our organisation and everything that we do and stand for...We couldn&rsquo;t have done it without you! The whole Flint team showed such dedication, professionalism, patience and positivity in getting us from a waffly wish-list to a beautiful site&quot;.  </p><p>The team at Flint were also inspired to get their hands dirty and recently held a chive growing competition. Unfortunately, we&#39;re only amateur gardeners at best but we do love a good competition!</p>]]></news-item-body><news-item-hero-image><![CDATA[<photos></photos>]]></news-item-hero-image><news-item-photos><![CDATA[<photos></photos>]]></news-item-photos></news-item><news-item news-item-id="23"><news-item-title><![CDATA[Flint welcomes two new team members!]]></news-item-title><news-item-publish-date><![CDATA[2010-10-29]]></news-item-publish-date><news-item-body><![CDATA[We&#39;re happy to announce that we have two new team members at Flint. Joining our hardworking web developer team is Matthieu. He hails from France but has traveled extensively and is now calling Melbourne home. We also welcome Merryn to our team. She is our new project manager and we&#39;ve thrown her into the deep end as we head into a busy and productive period at Flint. They are settling in well and we&#39;ll soon get Oli our resident photographer to put their lovely portraits on our website.]]></news-item-body><news-item-hero-image><![CDATA[<photos></photos>]]></news-item-hero-image><news-item-photos><![CDATA[<photos></photos>]]></news-item-photos></news-item><news-item news-item-id="24"><news-item-title><![CDATA[Chocolateria San Churro website coming in 2011!]]></news-item-title><news-item-publish-date><![CDATA[2010-11-16]]></news-item-publish-date><news-item-body><![CDATA[<p>Flint is working with super talented designer Mark O&#39;Keeffe of Mark Design on the new website for this iconic and delicious brand. With 21 stores nationwide, San Churro is Australia&#39;s fastest growing chocolate cafe and the new site will entice users share their love for all things cocoa and learn about the secret of real chocolate. Keep an eye out for this site in January 2011.</p>]]></news-item-body><news-item-hero-image><![CDATA[<photos></photos>]]></news-item-hero-image><news-item-photos><![CDATA[<photos></photos>]]></news-item-photos></news-item><news-item news-item-id="25"><news-item-title><![CDATA[Elle Macpherson - celebrating 30 years as a fashion icon by entering the digital age]]></news-item-title><news-item-publish-date><![CDATA[2010-11-01]]></news-item-publish-date><news-item-body><![CDATA[<p>Flint has again teamed up with Three60 Design to create this stunning classic website for Elle Macpherson. As she enters the thirtieth year of her career, Elle wanted to explore a new medium in which to showcase her work. Flint worked our Flash magic to bring her ideas to life and provided Elle with a Content Management System in which she can maintain her archive and utilise the website as a &quot;channel of expression&quot; of the people and things that inspire her. Be sure to check out the incredible image gallery archive, documenting the career of this iconic Australian model and business woman. </p><p>Click <a href="/work/project-information/elle-macpherson">here</a> for project information. </p>]]></news-item-body><news-item-hero-image><![CDATA[<photos></photos>]]></news-item-hero-image><news-item-photos><![CDATA[<photos></photos>]]></news-item-photos></news-item><news-item news-item-id="26"><news-item-title><![CDATA[Flint brings Kinetic IT into the twenty-first century]]></news-item-title><news-item-publish-date><![CDATA[2010-10-19]]></news-item-publish-date><news-item-introduction><![CDATA[<p>Websites have come a long way in the last few years and more and more businesses are promoting their services on the internet but it can still seem like a daunting task for those who have no idea how to start the process. When Kinetic IT approached Flint to create their website, we were more than happy to guide them on how to make the most of their presence online.   </p><p>Based in Perth, Kinetic IT is an industry leader with over 400 employees, providing operational management and support for their customers&#39; Information Communications and Technology (ICT) infrastructure. One of their key asks for their new website was that it would communicate the organisation&#39;s unique perspective on the industry and reflect its personality and values. </p><p> The result is a dynamic website, with great use of flash animation, that makes the company and what they do accessible to their customers as well as highlighting the &#39;Kinetic IT difference&#39; that sets them apart.  </p><p>We were delighted when Anthea from Kinetic IT gave us her feedback: &quot;We can&rsquo;t thank you and your team enough for walking with us to bring Kinetic IT into the 21st century online. Working with such a professional bunch of people made this process an absolute pleasure, you surprised and delighted us at every stage and exceeded our expectations. We are so proud of our new website, and would recommend Flint to any business that wants to capture their unique essence online&quot; </p><p>Read more about the project <a href="/work/project-information/kinetic-it">here</a> </p>]]></news-item-introduction><news-item-hero-image><![CDATA[<photos></photos>]]></news-item-hero-image><news-item-photos><![CDATA[<photos></photos>]]></news-item-photos></news-item></news-item-result>